horse.com 2011-12-05

# Privacy Policy - Horse.com

Our Privacy Pledge    

### Privacy Policy

Please review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may update it occasionally. Obviously, we will handle your information according to the terms of the Policy in effect at the time you give it to us. This policy was last updated on 02/10/2010.

What information do we collect about you?

Our information collection policy is simple: we only collect the information needed to provide you the products and services that you request in the best way that we can.

When you visit our web site, we automatically collect your Internet service provider's address, the web page that you came from and your activity while on our site.

When you make a purchase or request a catalog, we collect the information that you provide such as your name, address, phone number, email, order details and payment information.

When you register on our site, we collect all of the information that you volunteer, such as your name, address, phone number, email, and your interests. Please note: Not all of this information is required to register on our site. Required fields are denoted with a "*".

We also collect the information you provide us when you respond to a survey, contest or sweepstakes, or when you contact us by e-mail, phone, fax or mail.

If you arrive at our web site through a link from a third party site, you may have been redirected to our site through an intermediary site which may have recorded the internet protocol (IP) "address" of your browser, which address identifies the computer used, but does not permit identification of the individual using the computer. In addition, during such redirection a "cookie" or similar tracking device may have been placed on your hard drive through your Web browser.

Back To Top

How do we use your information?

The information that you provide allows us to serve you better by providing you with a convenient, personalized shopping experience. We use your information to process your order, update you on order status and customize the content of our web pages.

We also add your information to our customer database, so you may receive periodic mailings from us about new products and services or special promotions. If you do not want to receive these mailings from us, please contact us online  with the subject line "Unsubscribe".

You may also receive periodic promotional emails from us. If you do not want to receive such emails from us, please contact us online  with the subject line "Unsubscribe". Or click the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of every promotional email we send to you. Please note: You will still receive emails from us that are necessary to process your order or respond to your requests.

Occasionally, we may provide your name and postal address (but not your email address or phone number) to a select group of companies whose products may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to share your name and postal information with these companies, please contact us online. 

Also, we must share your information with third party companies to provide products and services to you such as packaging and shipping your order. We only share the information that is needed for the third party company to provide the necessary product or service, and all of our third party companies are contractually-restricted from using your information for any reason other than helping us to provide the necessary product or service. In the event that you arrive at our site through a link from a third party site, we may share limited information provided by you with that third party site to allow us to manage and administer our marketing affiliate program.

Back To Top

What are cookies and how do we use them?

Cookies are very small data files that the website creates on your hard drive to hold the information about your visit. We use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to understand traffic patterns so that we can improve the site to better meet the needs of our customers. The cookie does not hold personal or credit card information. The cookie will last up to one year after its creation on your computer, but can be deleted at any time. Please note: A cookie cannot be used to get data from your hard drive or gather personal information that you do not wish to share. In the event that you arrive at our website through a link from a third party site, cookies may be used by us or the affiliate marketing network company we use to determine whether and when you return to our site directly.

Back To Top

How can you access and update your information?

You may access and update the following information by logging into your secure account on our webstore, using your email and password:

  * Contact information (name, address, phone number)
  * Login information (email and password)
  * Shipping information (stored shipping names and addresses)
  * Payment information (credit cards and billing addresses. This information is only stored for future shopping at your request.)
  * Personal preferences (information you supplied on your interests)
  * Order information (prior orders and order status) 

You may also access this information by calling or writing to us (see Contact Us below). We will authenticate each request and reply in a manner that ensures the security of the information you have requested.

Back To Top

How do we keep your information secure?

When you shop at our webstore, rest assured that the transaction is secure. Our servers use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an advanced encryption technology that works with Netscape Navigator (versions 2.0 and above), Microsoft Internet Explorer (version 3.0 and above), and AOL (AOL 3.0 and above).

We use this technology on any pages that request personal information. A solid key or locked padlock symbol in the lower portion of your browser window shows that you are in this "secure mode." If you do not see this symbol on pages that request sensitive information, please call our Customer Service Center toll free at 1.800.637.6721 to complete your order.

We regret that we cannot guarantee that information transmitted through email will be secure, however, since email sent over the Internet is not secure. To discuss any sensitive information, please call Customer Service at 1.800.637.6721 instead of emailing us.

Back To Top

Children's Policy

TabCom, LLC does not solicit information from anyone under the age of fourteen, i.e., a "child." Any information that we receive from a user that is identified as a child will be deleted and not used for any purpose.

Back To Top

Marketing Information

We currently contract with several online partners to help manage and optimize our Internet business and communications. We use the services of a marketing company to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our site. To do this, we use Web beacons and cookies provided by our marketing company on this site. The type of information we collect includes product codes and prices for merchandise as well as which pages users have visited. By supplementing our records, this information helps us learn things like what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which of our products most interest our customers and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. Although our marketing company logs the information coming from our site on our behalf, we control how the data may and may not be used. If you do not want to help us learn how to improve our site, products, offers and marketing strategy, you can "opt-out" of this website analysis tool by clicking [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

Back To Top

Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about our policies or to have your name and information removed from any of TabCom, LLC's lists or databases, please contact us anytime at:

**Phone:** 1.888.653.0026 (customer service number)

**Email:** Contact us online 

**Mail:** TabCom, LLC  
Privacy Policy Administration  
1 Maplewood Drive  
Hazleton, PA 18202-9798

Back To Top
